

CEDRIC ANGELO SINA-ON

CONTACT:

+63 912 676 8592

ADDRESS:

Fairville Subd. Santa Barbara

EMAIL:

cao.sinaon@gmail.com

NATIONALITY:

Filipino

STATUS / BIRTH DATE:

Single / October 11, 2000

Greetings,

It is great pleasure of forwarding my CV for my further application, to provide you the facts of my skills and accomplishments. But a certain personal interview would be characterizing more to expose my desire and my capabilities.

My record of academic achievements and specialized career history express my attribution that makes me a valuable employee.

- 6 years of progressive experience in languages such as, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, PHP, Javascript - JQuery and AJAX.
- I also have an interest in data analytics using Python libraries.
- Computer literate; Knowledgeable in Microsoft Offices such as, MS Word, MS Excel, and PowerPoint.
- Excellent typing speed, written and communication skills.

I would truly like to discuss opportunities with you and thank you for your time and consideration, and I'm looking forward to your positive response.

Sincerely yours, **Cedric**

CAREER OBJECTIVE

A work that enhance my knowledge and skill and to work for an organization that will provide me the opportunity to be a part of a team. To contribute my expertise in the success of the company and to obtain on other responsibility in due time.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

SY 2019 – 2023	Bachelor of Science in Information Technology Iloilo Science and Technology University, La Paz, Iloilo City, Philippines College Diploma
SY 2017 – 2019	Iloilo National High School – Senior High School Diploma La Paz, Iloilo City, Iloilo City, Philippines
SY 2013 – 2017	Santa Barbara National Comprehensive High School – High School Diploma Roosevelt Street, Santa Barbara, Iloilo, Philippines
SY 2007 – 2013	Casa Bambini De Sta. Barbara Learning Center – Elementary Diploma Taft Street, Santa Barbara, Iloilo, Philippines

CERTIFICATES, TRAINING & SEMINAR

- Python for Machine Learning & Data Science Masterclass, Pierian Data Udemy -June 2023
- The Complete SQL Bootcamp From Zero to Hero in SQL, Pierian Data Udemy May 2023
- The Complete Python Bootcamp From Zero to Hero in Python, Pierian Data Udemy May 2023
- Student Internship Program, Kabertek Inc. –29th May, 2023
- INDUSTRY TRENDS: Innovations in Mission-critical communications and information solutions, AirNav Technologies Services, Frequentis 17th February 2023.

SKILLS

- Knowledgeable in Microsoft Offices such as, MS Word, Ms Excel, and PowerPoint.
- Web Development HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, PHP, Javascript JQuery and AJAX.
- Data Analytics Python, NumPy, Pandas, Matplotlib, and Seaborn.
- IDEs NetBeans, VS Code, Jupyter Notebook, Sublime Text (text editor)
- Windows installation, Hardware installation, basic troubleshooting.
- Self-assured in verbal and written English and/or Filipino communication.

CAREER HISTORY

Kabertek Inc. Iloilo, Philippines (February 2023 – May 2023) **Student Intern**

DUTIES & RESPONSIBILITIES

- Ensured strict adherence to guidelines for validating and encoding information.
- Prioritized data integrity by implementing robust measures.
- Diligently maintained confidentiality while handling sensitive information.
- Developed modules for established systems utilizing C# within an MVC framework.

Iloilo Science and Technology University La Paz Iloilo, Philippines (April 2022 - January 2023)
Student Assistant

DUTIES & RESPONSIBILITIES

- Assisted professors on daily classes and activities.
- Proficiently handled networking tasks including setup, configuration, and maintenance.
- Conducted system installations and performed troubleshooting, ensuring optimal PC performance.

REFERENCES

• LORHIL B. SALABE

Computer Technician Iloilo Science and Technology University Technical Support Office Iorhills@gmail.com

CHRISTIAN JESSIE CAPIANGAO

Executive Assistant
Kabertek Inc.
marvin.aguirre@kabertek.com

MARVIN AGUIRRE

Senior Consultant Kabertek Inc. jessie.capiangao@kabertek.com